tasmeemme.com 2013-06-05

# TasmeemME - Privacy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 1st April 2009.

Please take a few moments to read through the Privacy Policy indicated below.

TasmeemMe’s Privacy Policy is firmly committed to try and protect the privacy of all our registered users. TasmeemME’s Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use any personal information you share, and to help you make informed decisions when using our services.

By using or accessing TasmeemME; this means you are automatically accepting the guideline practices and conditions described in this Privacy Policy and must be aware that our policies may evolve and be revised in the future.

When you visit TasmeemMe’s site you will provide us with the personal information you want to disclose which is collected by us.

By using or accessing TasmeemME, you are accepting the practices described in our Privacy Policy.

### Information Collected

When you visit TasmeemME you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site.

When you register with TasmeemME, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your address, your gender, schools attended, etc.

When you use TasmeemME you set up a profile page and portfolio, you connect to other Talents, send message, and perform searches. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your contact list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.

Any user content posted on TasmeemME is done so at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of others who may view and comment on your work. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on TasmeemME is a violation of the TasmeemME Terms of Service and should be reported to [info@tasmeemME.com](mailto:info@tasmeemme.com).

By using TasmeemME, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States of America.

### Children under Age 16

TasmeemME does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 16 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 16, please do not attempt to register for TasmeemME or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 16 may provide any personal information to or on TasmeemME. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 16, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at [info@tasmeemME.com](mailto:info@tasmeemme.com).

### Children between the Ages of 16 and 18

We recommend that minors over the age of 16 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

### Use of Information Obtained by TasmeemME

When you register with TasmeemME, you create your own profile. Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed to people in the networks enable you to connect with people on TasmeeemME. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications.

Profile information is used by TasmeemME primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to others permitted to view that information. TasmeemMe is not responsible and does not control the use of the content and information displayed and provided by others. 

TasmeemME may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, if a connection sends you a new message or there is a new job post in your field, you may receive an email.

TasmeemME may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating statistics.

### Links

TasmeemME may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by TasmeemME.

### Changing or Removing Information

Access and control over most personal information on TasmeemME is readily available through the profile editing tools. TasmeemME users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately, once the new information is saved. If changes have not been made or saved, then the old information data will not be changed. Individuals who wish to deactivate their TasmeemME account may do so by sending an email to [info@tasmeemME.com](mailto:info@tasmeemme.com). Removed information may persist in backup copies but will not be generally available to members of TasmeemME.

Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on TasmeemME, however, (e.g., sending a personal message to another TasmeemME user) you generally cannot remove such communications. Public comments whether in a message or on a posted work item cannot be deleted. Such comments will remain there indefinitely.

### Security

TasmeemME takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of TasmeemME, please contact us at [info@tasmeemME.com](mailto:info@tasmeemme.com)

### Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of TasmeemME, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. Individuals continuing to use the website will signify that he/she are accepting the terms and conditions of the privacy policy of the website. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at [info@tasmeemME.com](mailto:info@tasmeemme.com).
